Choose Love is a romance, comedy film directed by Stuart McDonald.
The steady boyfriend.
The one who got away.
The charming rock star.
Who will Cami choose?
In this interactive rom-com, her love life is in your hands.
Cami Conway, played by Laura Marano.
Paul Swartz, played by Scott Michael Foster.
Rex Galier, played by Avan Jogia.
Jack Menna, played by Jordi Webber.
Amalia, played by Megan Smart.
Florian, played by Benjamin Hoetjes.
Choose Love is a 2023 interactive romantic comedy
film on streaming service Netflix.
Viewers make choices for the main character Cami, portrayed by Laura Marano, as she
questions her relationship with her partner Paul when two other men enter her life.
It was released on August 31, 2023, but was removed from
Netflix's catalogue on December 1, 2024.
It received a generally negative reception.
The film explores themes of romcom, interactive, romantic.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.